["Pursuit of Happiness
(Nightmare)" by Kid Cudi]
[man] Alright, who else?
[woman] Uh, we need
to have the Wilsons.
[man] Oh, shit!
-We can't forget the Wilsons.
-The Wilsons.
Anyone else?
Uh... Thank you.
Um, nope.
I think that is it.
Alrighty, then.
Shall we?
Clear?
All clear.
Uh-oh.
-No.
-Close call.
[chuckles]
Let's roll.
[beep]
[man on voicemail]
Hey,this is Mitch.
Please leave a message
and I'll get right back to you.
[woman panting]
[woman on recording]
Please, tell me you're okay.
I've been trying the resort,
but no-one's answering.
They're saying
on the news that...
I'm so scared.
I need you.
I love you.
I'll keep trying.
[dark sombre music]
[dark sombre music continues]
[Australian reporter] Tragic
images continue to emerge
following the US Military's
accidental deployment
of an experimental weapon
off the coast
of Tasmania last week,
which resulted
in the decimation of Hobart
and a total loss of life
across the island.
Protests in Washington, D.C.,
have escalated
as pressure from the UN and
the Australian Prime Minister
to hold the US President
to account
has reached fever pitch.
Just why news reporters can't
go into disaster zones...
[woman snores]
[intercom trills]
[pilot speaks indistinctly
over intercom]
[reporter
continues indistinctly]
I wasn't snoring, was I?
Not a peep.
[tinkling]
You know, apparently
they didn't feel a thing,
just kind of
drifted off to sleep.
Hopefully, he's one of
the lucky ones that wakes up.
[dark music]
[reporter continues]
...has started to take shape.
Stretching beyond the fireball
at the centre of the blast,
an electromagnetic pulse
resulted in the catastrophic
neural failure
of all living things
on the island,
causing their death.
We urgently need volunteers
to come to Tasmania
and assist in the aftermath
of this disaster.
This is a task of
unprecedented scale.
The nation calls upon you
to stand up
and to show
the resilient spirit...
-[man continues indistinctly]
-[woman breathes deeply]
[cadet] Our nation thanks you
for volunteering your services
during this dark time.
Please, place
your phone in the tub
and make your way over to
the hangar for registration.
Your phones
will be returned to you
upon departing the island.
Thank you!
-[truck engine churns]
-[cadet] Welcome to Devonport!
Our nation thanks you...
[continues indistinctly]
[helicopters whirr]
[people jostle and shout]
[tense music]
[people chatter busily]
[man] Next! Nice and quick.
Over there, please.
Is this information correct?
Is that you?
-[woman] Go grab your kit...
-[man shouting indistinctly]
-[woman] Next!
-I wanna see my fuckin' wife!
-We get it!
-[woman] Next!
[shouting continues]
Miss? ID. Hat off.
I'm here on a compassionate
grounds exemption.
I'd like to join
the body retrieval unit
down in the south
of the island.
I need to get to a small town
down there called Woodbridge.
No-one's going
south of Hobart yet.
Sorry?
The whole city's
still burning.
You're gonna have to sit tight
till the fires are out.
Look, stick with your unit.
You'll make it south
eventually.
[stammers]
Who was down there?
[tearfully] My husband.
I'm sorry.
It's just how it is.
Go grab your kit.
You'll be moving out soon
with Unit 209 just over there.
-Next, please!
-Listen.
I'm a physical therapist.
Maybe I could help out
with things while I wait.
Your exemption was for
disaster victim
identification,
body retrieval.
That's what you're doing
while you're
on the island
or you're heading home.
Is it true
what they're saying?
[captain] I'm sure
you've all heard the rumours
and I can confirm...
they're true.
In rare circumstances,
we're observing
unusual behaviour
from some of the deceased.
Now, we have no way of knowing
when a victim
may come back online.
But take it from me -
the lights are on,
no-one's home.
-[people muttering]
-Listen! Listen!
[all quieten]
If you happen
to come across a victim
who's showing signs
of activity,
the military will be there
to take care of them,
efficiently,
with the dignity they deserve.
The odd ones
that do come back online,
I can assure you they
are docile, slow moving.
You have nothing to fear.
So just stay calm
and let us do our job.
[solemn dreamy music]
[speaks indistinctly]
-[dreamy music continues]
-[chatter over radio]
Hey, mate?
Hey, mate? Can I just...
How many of them
have actually come back?
Look.
If you come across one,
pop your flare,
me and the boys
will come in, sort it out.
Hey, you'll be alright.
Why only some of them?
It's gonna be okay.
[breathes shakily]
[grim music]
[indistinct chatter
over radio]
[grim music intensifies]
[engine rumbles]
[bus brakes hiss]
[woman] Two to a house!
Partner up. Let's move!
Thank you. I want to see
a sense of urgency, people!
Move!
[people chattering busily]
[uneasy music]
[wind chimes tinkling]
[woman] Over here!
[footsteps thud softly]
[woman] You know, it was hard
saying goodbye to them, but...
I felt like I had
to pitch in down here.
What about you? Got kids?
[soft music]
No.
[children's voices
echo faintly]
[sombre music]
[woman] I'll check upstairs!
[footsteps thud]
[breathes shallowly]
[music builds]
[water running]
[breathes shakily]
[breathing slows and echoes]
[dark music]
[tractor rumbles]
[exhales heavily]
[wind blusters]
Hey, are you okay?
Uh, I need to, um...
I need to go.
I need to hug my girls.
-Okay.
-[camera clicks]
[helicopter whirrs]
[door thuds]
[man retches]
Sorry, mate.
I'm fuckin' done.
[man spits and retches]
You're gonna need
to find someone else.
[man coughs and gags]
[door slams open]
[whistles] Anyone home?
Are you there? Oi!
I don't get it.
Why do only some of them
come back, not all of them?
[man] Fucked if I know.
Poor bastards.
Imagine having to die twice.
[grunts] Fuck that.
Are you just gonna
fuckin' stand there or what?
Fuck.
[woman] Oh, doesn't
the smell bother you?
-Of course it does.
-Where's your mask?
[man scoffs]
How's that thing
working out for ya?
Is it fuckin' cherry-flavoured
or something? Up!
[angelic Italian opera music]
[grunts]
[angelic music continues]
[water running]
[grunts]
[angelic music continues]
[sighs]
[both strain and grunt]
[fabric ripping]
Great. Fucking great!
-Where are you going?
-To shit.
-Is that okay with you?
-Now?
I don't know. Find some
fucking rope or something.
Horsepower's the only way
we're getting
her fat fucking arse
out of here.
[grunts]
[door thuds]
[soft melancholy music]
With this ring, I...
If I can get it on.
Uh, I bind my life
to yours... forever.
[toilet flushes]
[woman] Do you know there was
a chicken called Miracle Mike
who went on living
for 18 months
after they chopped
its head off?
-[man] Oh, get fucked.
-[woman] Nah, it's true.
The farmer who tried
killing it aimed too high
and left, like, a little bit
of its brain intact
'cause, you know, birds have
these, like, big eye sockets
so the brain
can't fit in the skull
so part of it gets
squished into its neck.
Headless chooks...
What are you talkin' about?
Well, don't you reckon
they could learn so much
about, like,
neural pathways and all that
if they studied
one of the ones coming back,
instead of just
blowing their heads off?
I'll give you the hot tip,
alright?
You can think about this, that
and a third, all you want -
but while we're here,
we stick together.
-[woman 2] He's gonna wake up!
-You get me?
He is! I know he is!
He's gonna wake up!
-He's gonna wake up... No!
-[soldier speaks indistinctly]
Wake up! Wake up!
[soldier] Come on.
[woman weeps] No!
Wake up. Oh, my boy!
My boy...
[woman sobs]
[sorrowful pensive music]
[man] What?
So like a masseuse?
No, not like a masseuse.
Like a physical therapist.
So you don't do massage?
Uh, there's massage involved.
My shoulder's been killing me
since we started lifting
all these dead fucks.
You reckon you can
take a look?
-Uh, maybe.
-Awesome!
-Thanks, Ava.
-I said maybe.
[gentle music]
[heartbeat echoes]
[knock at door]
[door opens]
[trembles]
[Mitch] It'll happen.
I promise.
We have all the time
in the world.
[whistle trilling]
-[woman outside] Hey! Here!
-[man outside] Oi, hurry up!
-Hurry up!
-He's in there! He's in there!
[soldier] Go, go, go!
[man] Fuck this!
Oh, don't fucking help!
-[gunshots]
-Oh!
[indistinct shouting]
[door creaks]
[man whistles softly]
Hey, GTS Monaro. Fuck me!
Someone looked after you.
[keys jangle]
[car door opens]
[splattering]
Clay.
[car door shuts]
[unearthly music]
Righto.
[garage door rattles]
[unearthly music continues]
[Clay] Oi!
They're coming.
[unearthly music continues]
[muted gunshots]
Go forth on your journey
from this world,
in the name of the Father,
the Son and the Holy Spirit.
-Amen.
-[bell rings]
[trucks rumbling
and beeping in distance]
[pensive music]
[pensive music continues]
[Mitch's voice echoes]
Come on!
Let's go!
[helicopters whirr]
[pensive music intensifies]
Fuck.
[muffled chatter in distance]
[man shouts joyfully]
[people whoop and cheer]
[rock music
plays loudly in distance]
[people chant and cheer]
[man] Keep it down, you lot!
Some of us
are trying to sleep!
[man 2] Fuck you!
[music and chatter
in distance]
[helicopter whirrs outside]
[woman] Going somewhere?
I was just getting some air.
That's what
the courtyard's for.
[indistinct chatter on radio]
Surprised we let any Yanks
chip in at all.
Ask me,
should've been a blanket ban.
[rock music
continues in distance]
Go blow off some steam
with that lot.
[rock music continues]
[cheering and shouting]
[people shout]
Four, three, two, one!
[cheering and laughter]
[Clay] Well, Ava,
here's to all the Lady
Mc-fucking-lard-arses
and their narrow
fucking hallways.
Who knows what beautiful
sights and smells
awaits us tomorrow?
[people cheer]
So what's so special
in Hobart, then?
My husband.
Ugh.
He was at a work retreat
just south of there
at a town on the coast
called Woodbridge.
[stammers]
The man in the garage today,
he seemed like
he wasn't fully gone,
like a part of him
was still there,
like he was lost, scared.
I saw a guy covered
in fuckin' motor oil
who just came back
from the dead.
Didn't spend too long
gazing into his eyes.
He looked at me, right at me.
He seemed more
than just nerve endings,
more than just
a chicken without its head.
-If Mitch is like that...
-Then what?
Goodnight, Clay.
[American accent]
Till tomorrow, partner!
[banging]
[creaking and scraping]
[scraping and thudding]
[roars]
[helicopter whirrs outside]
[dark music]
[door rattles]
[Clay] Holy fucking shit!
What a fucking beauty!
I gotta figure out
how to get this bad boy
past the higher-ups.
Give my fuckin' left nut
to take her for a spin, hey?
What do you reckon
they'd throw at me?
Talking months or years?
Anyway...
...good chat.
Jesus Christ.
[Clay] Fuck me dead! [scoffs]
Some way to end
a fuckin' buck's.
Check out the groom-to-be.
[Clay scoffs]
[Ava] Best day ever.
[Clay] What goes
on tour, right? Yoink!
[clears throat]
[sniffs] Oh.
Do you fancy a bump?
A little early for me.
Hmph.
So you ride, huh?
Been dicking around on
dirt bikes since I was a kid.
Never got the chance on
something like that, though.
[Ava] On something like that,
there might be a way
around the worst of it.
[Clay] The worst of what?
The roads,
the smoke, the army.
The main arteries
will be a mess,
but once we get
to Mount Wellington,
it looks like there are some
narrow roads we could take.
If we stick to the suburbs
that are already cleared
there should be a way
to get to the highway
without them spotting us.
We're... we're 200 miles
from the Enso Resort.
Leave now, get a good
enough run, who knows?
Could be there later today.
You'd get to take her
for one hell of a spin
and wouldn't even have
to give up your left nut.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Just wait up, Ava.
You might've signed up
to this to find your hubby,
but I want to make
a difference.
My country needs me.
The dead need me.
[laughs] I'm just
fucking with you.
-Mmm, I'll find some helmets.
-Really?
Yeah, we'll need
a full tank too.
Whoo! Alright,
let's fucking roll.
[bottle clinks and rattles]
[Ava breathes shallowly]
[crackling and gurgling]
[helicopter
whirrs loudly outside]
[grating and crackling]
[gnashing]
[crackling]
[softly] Can you hear?
[crack]
Ava! What are you doing?
Get the fuck away from it!
[gnashing]
[low tense music]
[helicopter whirrs
in distance]
[indistinct chatter on radio]
[people chattering]
["Hertz"
by Amyl and the Sniffers]
♪ I wanna go see the country
♪ I want to get out
of here... ♪
[Clay] Whoo!
♪ I'm sick
of lookin' at graffiti
♪ On the walls of
the grey walls, the city... ♪
-You good?
-Yeah.
♪ I want the breeze in my hair
♪ I am touching your leg and
♪ I have my hand in your hand
♪ Take me to the beach,
take me to the country
♪ Climb in the back seat
if you love me
♪ Hire me a car,
I wanna go driving
♪ Climb in the back seat... ♪
[Clay] Tuck it in!
[engine revs]
♪ That's where you'll find me
♪ I want you to love me... ♪
[brakes squeal]
♪ Do you love me? ♪
-[Ava] Oh!
-Shit.
-[engines rumble]
-[Clay] Quick. Over there!
Come on, come on, come on!
[engines rev]
[tyres squeal]
[uneasy music]
[gunshot]
[soldiers shout]
[engines rumble]
[engines fade]
[pensive music]
[foreboding music rises]
[motorcycle engine roars]
[Clay coughs]
Fuckin' masks! [coughs]
Where the fuck are they?
[coughs]
-[Ava wheezes]
-Got 'em!
-[crackling and gnashing]
-Fucking hell.
[squelching and cracking]
[coughs]
[engine revs]
[cracking]
[eerie music]
[music intensifies]
[music fades]
[motorcycle engine
whirrs in distance]
[engine stops]
[water dripping]
[tap squeaks, water runs]
[Clay grunts]
Fuck.
[groans]
Fuck me.
[Ava] Hm, okay, you win.
[Clay] Really?
[winces] Oh, fuck!
-Want me to stop?
-No, no, keep going.
Whatever you're doing
hurts like fucking fuck,
but please keep going.
-[crack]
-Mmm!
There, there, there,
there, there. Fuck me.
So how long
you been doing this, then?
Almost six years.
Just recently opened
my own clinic.
What about your hubby?
What did he do?
He's in renewable energy.
Every year, delegates from
the company he works for
have a big meet-up.
This time around,
it was someone's
bright idea to pick Tasmania.
Huh. Shit, hey?
What about you?
I'm a builder. I got my own
little business in Melbourne.
I was putting the frames up
on this old duck's reno
when she brought me over
to the TV to watch the news.
Did you lose anyone close?
You hit the spot, Ava.
I think I'm all good.
[thud]
[cracking]
[heavy footsteps]
[Clay] Where the hell
did he wander in from?
[unsettling music]
Buddy, we're closed! Go be
a dead cunt somewhere else.
[gnashing]
[terrifying music]
[gunshot]
[Clay mutters] Fuckin' hell.
[low gnashing]
I noticed a pattern
with ones like him.
The longer they go on,
the more agitated they become.
[grinding]
They start to lash out.
[squelch]
[squishing]
What are you two
doing down here?
Taroona's restricted.
The whole south is.
We're from body retrieval.
I'm looking for someone.
Who?
My husband.
And you? What's your story?
-He's...
-I'm helping her get there.
Chauffeur.
And where's that?
Woodbridge.
How'd you make it
through Hobart?
Wasn't easy, mate.
We had to find our way
around the smoke.
It nearly cost us
our lungs, didn't it?
Hmm.
That's some bike
you got there.
Yeah, she was a little dusty,
but she'll be better
for the run.
Take it for a spin.
Come with me.
He needs to make
an official statement.
So do you, so wait in there.
Chow down on whatever you
want and we'll be right back.
It's alright, Ava.
It was fun while it lasted.
[soldier] Sit tight.
[door shuts and locks]
Let's go.
[Clay] So it's just you all
alone out here, is it, mate?
-No unit?
-Into the kitchen.
[Clay] Hey, listen, I know
you've got to follow protocol,
but can't we just
keep this in-house?
No harm, no foul, right?
[pensive music]
[doorknob rattles]
[breathes shakily]
I'm sorry, Mitch.
[metal clinks]
[pensive music continues]
[footsteps approach]
[Mitch] Why didn't you
pick up when I called?
[keys jangle]
[sighs]
You said you wanted
to talk, so let's talk.
[footsteps approach]
[lock clicks]
[door opens]
Some mate you got there.
Bloke did a bloody runner.
Said he needed to take a piss.
I gave him
the benefit of the doubt
and he left me in the dust.
Spent the last couple of hours
trying to find him.
They'll throw
the book at him now.
Look, Ava.
I know what
you're going through.
Closure is important.
So I'm gonna give you safe
passage through to Woodbridge.
But...
if you find your husband...
I hope you understand
what that could mean.
And I also need to know that
you're not gonna do a runner.
I... I'm not. I promise.
We just need to pick up
a few things first, alright?
[low tense music]
[Ava sighs]
[engine rumbles]
[tense music continues]
How much further?
Almost there.
[tense music continues]
[engine revs]
The place was run by
an old farmer and his wife.
The whole place
was stocked with canned food
before I stationed here.
I found some meat
in the freezer.
Another day or two
before it turns.
[engine rumbles]
[brakes squeak]
[engine shuts off]
[soldier] Well, come on.
I'm a half-decent cook
when I want to be.
I thought you were just
picking up some things.
I'm running on fumes.
So, let's grab something
while we're here.
[door shuts]
[footsteps recede]
[cutlery clinks]
Don't let it get cold.
Try some of the corn.
"If you're hungry,
you'll eat anything."
That's what my dad
drilled into me since day dot.
He was an army man too.
He actually met a colonel once
who was right there
when you Yanks
first started toying around
with that pulse technology.
Hmph.
Of all the patches of ocean
they could've tried it
out on, hey?
It still doesn't seem real.
Katie.
My wife.
We were expecting our first.
A little boy,
only a couple of weeks away.
She was down here visiting
her folks in Queenstown.
You don't mind if I...
I was part
of a training exercise
up in a place called
Townsville on the mainland.
You know it?
[lighter clicks]
As soon as I heard
the island wasn't radioactive,
I talked my way onto one of
the first choppers down here.
Found them in the house.
[sighs] Katie's
childhood home.
[breathes shakily]
They were all, uh...
sitting around
the kitchen table,
middle of breakfast.
Toast rack was still full.
I picked out a nice-looking
tree in the backyard.
This dinky little swing Katie
used to have as a girl
still hanging from it.
Started digging.
Made it all as nice
as I could for 'em.
I'm sorry.
People, when they get sick,
you know, terminal...
their loved ones,
they get that... that moment,
the long goodbye.
The way this went down,
the rug getting pulled
like it did...
I don't know.
It was a special
kind of cruel.
It meant everything, getting
to see her for myself.
Don't know what
I would've done without that.
She didn't come back?
[exhales shakily]
When are we leaving?
Soon.
Before we get going,
there's, um...
something I need to ask you.
[tense music]
[inhales sharply]
[exhales]
[music builds]
[music intensifies]
[knock at door]
[soldier]
Uh, how's it going in there?
[music crescendos]
I'm ready.
My hair's a little wet. Sorry.
Your hair's fine.
You saw she was
a redhead anyway.
Just one dance. That's all.
If you don't mind.
[music plays faintly
on headphones]
[soldier exhales]
Here.
This will help.
["You Said Something"
by PJ Harvey]
♪ The Empire State Building
♪ And you said something
♪ That I've never forgotten
♪ We lean against railings
♪ Describing the colours
♪ And the smells
of our homelands
♪ Acting like lovers... ♪
[whispers] You're beautiful.
♪ How did we get here... ♪
I'm sorry, Katie.
I love you.
I'll always love you.
I'm sorry I couldn't
protect you.
Both of you.
I can feel him in there.
[chuckles]
Oh, what a trip.
That's not it.
You're not wearing it.
You...
The song's ending.
I told you to put everything
on, the ring as well.
The song's over.
Do you mind swapping it out?
You said one dance. We danced.
Now, please take me
to my husband.
But, uh...
But...
You ruined it. I...
You ruined everything.
Uh, I'm sorry.
It's... it's my fault.
I should have double-checked.
Uh... Can you
please put it on?
No. I'm not
taking my ring off.
[uneasy music]
We need to start again.
I'm not taking off my ring.
I'm not starting again.
Please. I played my part.
Put it on...
or our deal's over.
Stay back.
Ava...
I said stay back!
-[Ava pants]
-Arggh!
No...
-Hey, hey! Wait! No!
-[thudding on door]
-Ava!
-Stay the fuck away from me!
I'm not your fucking wife!
Leave me alone, please!
-[thudding continues]
-Leave me alone!
[soldier] Ava, open the door.
[thud]
Please, just come out of
there, okay? Let me explain.
Ava!
Oh, my God.
[grunts]
You want to know why only
some of them come back?
It's 'cause they're the ones
with unfinished business.
Like Katie.
She wasn't ready to go.
It wasn't her time yet.
All she wanted
was to be a mum.
And she will.
She'll be a great mum.
Ava, open the door.
Please, Ava.
You don't understand.
He's alive. I felt him kick.
He's waiting for his mum.
He's waiting for me.
Open the fuckin' door!
[grunts]
Ava! Open it!
Ava, come out of there!
Come out of there!
[thudding]
Just listen to me! Please!
[continues shouting
and banging]
[Ava grunts]
-[thudding inside]
-Ava!
[pants]
[lock rattles and squeaks]
[soft thud]
[sinister music]
Ava!
[door opens]
Ava?
Come on.
[crackling]
[gasps]
Ava?
[chains rattle]
[gnashing]
[soldier] Ava,
come out of there.
-[crackling and grinding]
-[soldier] It's not safe.
They're getting
more hostile by the day.
[chains rattle]
[soldier] Look.
I'm sorry, alright?
[teeth grinding]
[chains clink]
[gnashing]
Ava?
Ava, come on. Just come out
and we can make things right.
I said I'd take you
to your husband.
[grinding]
We can still do that.
[teeth crackling]
Just come out of there.
[gnashing]
Ava, come on.
You can't stay
in here all night.
Sweetie, I can't find my ring.
Did you see it?
[grinding and gurgling]
Shall we go get it?
Then we can finish our dance.
[crackling]
Come out of there.
[faint jangling]
Oh, you poor thing.
Let me patch you up.
Would you?
Of course.
[soldier trembles]
[teeth crackling]
It's too late, Ava.
You ruined it.
You shouldn't have ruined...
Ugh!
[splattering]
[soldier groans]
[body thuds]
[gurgling]
[gasps]
[sputters]
[keys jangle]
[pants]
[haunting music]
[engine churns]
[engine starts]
[haunting music continues]
[heartbeat echoes]
[engine rumbles]
Please, Mitch. Please stay.
[huffs]
I don't think that's
a good idea right now.
Well, at least let me
drive you to the airport.
No...
The car's almost here.
[zipper buzzes]
I'll be back in a week.
Let's talk then.
[footsteps recede]
[door shuts in distance]
[Ava murmurs]
[groans softly]
[wind whistles in distance]
[footsteps thud softly]
[exhales slowly]
[waves crashing]
[glass crunches]
[waves crashing in distance]
[crackling]
[footsteps crunch]
[glass crunches]
-[snarling]
-[gasps]
[gnashing]
Oh! [grunts]
[axe clatters]
[grunts]
[snarling and gnashing]
[Ava exclaims and grunts]
[terrifying music]
[Ava] Oh, please!
Arggh!
[grunts]
[pants heavily]
[cracking and snarling]
[grunts]
[screams]
[scream echoes and fades]
[door creaks]
[door thuds and rattles]
[metal groans]
[exhales]
[sighs]
[winces]
[moans]
[gasps]
[creaking outside]
[rattling]
[metal clangs]
[rattling continues]
[sharp scraping]
[wheezes]
[soft music]
[digging continues]
[low sorrowful music]
[grunts]
[sorrowful music continues]
[Mitch's voice]
Just a little further.
[Ava's voice]
[music builds]
[Ava grunts]
[muted whack]
[body thuds]
[pensive music]
[door creaks]
[soft music]
[snarling]
[crackling]
[thudding]
[door shuts]
[dark momentous music builds]
[door opens]
[door shuts]
[dark music continues]
[music fades]
Hi, babe.
[softly] I'm here.
[waves crashing faintly
in distance]
[door rattles]
[wind howls outside]
She's pretty.
Was pretty.
[Ava sighs]
Well...
...nothing to report?
No unfinished business?
Here I am.
I'm right here, Mitch.
We're just gonna leave
this giant fucking mess
the way it is?
Wake up.
Please, wake up.
Mitch?
Mitch, please.
Please, wake up.
Please.
[Ava weeps]
[dark music rises]
[muffled male voice] Ava?
Ava?
-Mitch?
-[door opens]
[waves crashing in distance]
[Ava] I wanted to start IVF.
He said we just
had to give it time.
We started fighting.
A lot.
I didn't know what we were
to each other anymore.
I hooked up with someone.
I told Mitch about it
before he flew down here.
I thought
if I could find him...
...any version of him...
...that I could
somehow fix things.
But I can't.
[Ava sniffles]
[sniffs]
[chuckles]
[inhales deeply]
Hannah, my daughter,
and her mum Bridgette.
They don't want
anything to do with me.
I thought I'd come down here.
Show them how selfless I am.
Thought maybe they'd see me
in a new light or something.
I called Bridgette and
told her I was pitching in.
A big fuckin' hero.
She told me to get fucked.
[liquid sloshes]
I came down anyway.
I thought I'd...
still show her.
[sighs] Believe it or not,
sometimes I just
can't get out of my own way.
Stupid.
Anyway...
how'd you get away
from that fuckin' psycho?
[Ava] You first.
["Vitamin C" by Can]
♪ Her daddy got
a big aeroplane
♪ Her mummy holds
all the family's cash
♪ A beautiful rose
♪ Standing at the corner
♪ She is living
in and out of tune... ♪
[both chatter indistinctly]
♪ Hey, you! ♪
[splash!]
[Ava laughs]
[song continues]
[both laugh and chatter]
[gnashing]
[snarling]
[bottle thuds]
♪ Hey, you! ♪
[grunts]
-[Clay] Ava...
-[grunting and yelling]
Ava!
[song fades]
[low snoring]
[waves crashing
faintly in distance]
[continues snoring]
[angelic Italian opera music]
[angelic music continues]
[both grunt and puff]
Phew! Just like
old times, hey, partner?
Are you gonna hurl?
[angelic music continues]
Oh, shit.
Sorry, Ava.
Are you fucking serious?
Sorry.
Fuck!
[angelic music continues]
[engine rumbles]
[music ends]
[brakes squeak]
[crackling]
[Clay sighs]
Your move, ginger.
I'll just go around her...
What the fuck are you doing?
[door opens]
Fuck.
Ava?
[low crackling]
[Clay] What's she waiting for?
[solemn music]
[crackling]
[woman breathing raggedly]
[gasping and panting]
[music rises]
[music fades]
[crying in distance]
[Clay] Ava!
[crying continues]
[tense music builds]
[pants]
[baby wailing]
[baby cries]
[music intensifies]
[baby fusses]
[gently] Hey.
Here.
Hey, hey.
Hey, you're okay.
-[baby fusses]
-Hey. [chuckles softly]
Hey.
[momentous music rises]
Hey, shh.
You're okay. You're okay.
Hey.
You're okay.
["Help I'm Alive" by Metric]
♪ Can you hear my heart
♪ Beating like a hammer?
♪ Beating
like a hammer?
♪ Help, I'm alive, my heart
keeps beating like a hammer
♪ Hard to be soft
♪ Tough to be tender
♪ Come take my pulse
♪ The pace is on
a runaway train
♪ Help, I'm alive,
my heart keeps
♪ Beating like a hammer
♪ Beating
like a hammer
♪ Beating like a hammer
♪ Beating
like a hammer
♪ Beating like a hammer
♪ Beating
like a hammer
♪ Help, I'm alive
♪ My heart keeps
beating like a hammer. ♪
[gentle music]